<resources>
    <string name="app_name">\n\n\n\n○・●・○・●・○・●・○・●・○・●・○</string>
    <string name="title"> ─◇ Animal Quiz ◇─ </string>
    <string name="intro">Can you tell your turtles from your tortoises? Let\'s find out!</string>
    <string name="swipe_right">Swipe right ➟ </string>
    <string name="question_one">Question One</string>
    <string name="question_two">Question Two</string>
    <string name="question_three">Question Three</string>
    <string name="question_four">Question Four</string>
    <string name="question_five">Question Five</string>
    <string name="question_six">Question Six</string>
    <string name="question_seven">Question Seven</string>
    <string name="question_eight">Question Eight</string>

    <string name="q1text">What animal is this? </string>
    <string name="q1alligator">Alligator</string>
    <string name="q1crocodile">Crocodile</string>
    <string name="q1Caiman">Caiman</string>
    <string name="q1Gharial">Gharial</string>

    <string name="q2text">Which big cat is this?</string>
    <string name="q2leopard">Leopard</string>
    <string name="q2cheetah">Cheetah</string>
    <string name="q2jaguar">Jaguar</string>

    <string name="q3text">Is this a porpoise or a dolphin?</string>
    <string name="q3Porpoise">Porpoise</string>
    <string name="q3Dolphin">Dolphin</string>

    <string name="q4text">Are these llamas or alpacas?</string>
    <string name="q4llama">Llamas</string>
    <string name="q4alpaca">Alpacas</string>

    <string name="q5text">Is this a toad or a frog?</string>
    <string name="q5text2">Select up to two answers</string>
    <string name="q5toad">Toad</string>
    <string name="q5frog">Frog</string>
    <string name="q5prince">Prince</string>

    <string name="q6text">Which type of animal is this?</string>
    <string name="q6text2">Select two correct answers:</string>
    <string name="lizard">Lizard</string>
    <string name="amphibian">Amphibian</string>
    <string name="salamander">Salamander</string>
    <string name="reptile">Reptile</string>

    <string name="q7text">Which animal is this?</string>
    <string name="q7bar">Type your answer here</string>

    <string name="submitAnswers">Press me!</string>

    <string name="scoreDeclare">Out of 7 points, you scored:</string>

    <string name="pattern">○・●・○・●・○・●・○・●・○・●・○</string>

    <string name="results">─◇ Results ◇─</string>
    <string name="comments">Well Done!</string>
    <string name="explanation">Not sure about some of the answers? Here are some differences among
        our commonly confused creatures:</string>

    <string name="res1"> Question 1 </string>
    <string name="res1a">Correct answer: Alligator</string>
    <string name="res2"> Question 2 </string>
    <string name="res2a">Correct answer: Leopard</string>
    <string name="res3">Question 3</string>
    <string name="res3a">Correct answer: dolphin</string>
    <string name="res4">Question 4</string>
    <string name="res4a">Correct answer: Alpacas</string>
    <string name="res5">Question 5</string>
    <string name="res5a">Correct answer: Toad</string>
    <string name="res6">Question 6</string>
    <string name="res6a">Correct answer: Salamander, Amphibian</string>
    <string name="res7">Question 7</string>
    <string name="res7a">Correct answer: Sea lion</string>

    <string name="ex1"> The simplest way to tell between these reptiles is by the shape of their snout.
    Alligators and caimans have more rounded snouts, whilst a crocodile\'s is closer to a \'V\' shape. However
        gharials have a distinctive snout which is much thinner and longer.These prehistoric looking
        creatures also belong to different families, with alligators and caimans being part of the alligatoridae family,
    crocodiles within crocodylidae, and gharials within the closely related group of Gavialidae. </string>
    
    <string name="ex2"> This group is beautifully spotted but have many distinctions. A cheetah is found
    mainly in African and Asian grasslands and is the smallest and lightest of the group, built
    for speed and holding the title as the fastest land animal. It has dark spots which are solid and round, unlike the
    rosette shapes of leopards, which live across Africa, Middle East and Asia. Jaguars are found across the Americas
    and also have rosette shaped spots, but are larger in size and stronger than leopards.</string>

    <string name="ex3">The main differences between dolphins and porpoises are in the shapes of their bodies.
        Dolphins have elongated beaks whilst porpoises have rounded beaks. Dolphins also have longer bodies.
    However, both species are very intelligent, with large, complex brains and have a structure in
        their forehead which generates sound waves, helping them to navigate underwater.</string>

    <string name="ex4">Alpacas are small- a llama is almost twice the size of
    an alpaca. Alpacas have smaller ears, whilst llamas have large ears that point forward. Alpacas
         also have denser, yet softer coats. This is because they were bred for wool, whilst llamas
    were often used to carry heavy loads or guard premises, including guarding herds
    of alpacas. Llamas are known to spit when they feel threatened, but alpacas, with a more gentle nature,
    rarely do this.</string>

    <string name="ex5">Toads and frogs can often be differentiated by their skin and legs. Generally, frogs have
    smooth skin covered in a layer of mucus, whilst toads have a rougher, thicker skin. Due to their
        skin type, frogs need to stay closer to water sources than toads, which require less moisture.
        Frogs also have longer legs and often move by jumping, unlike toads which usually crawl.</string>

    <string name="ex6"> Lizards are reptiles, but salamanders are amphibians, which give them several
        distinctions. Salamanders are found in habitats that contain moisture and water, whilst lizards
        are adapted to hotter climates, often basking in the sun and requiring little water to survive.
        This leads to differences in skin composition, with lizards having dry skin and scales, whilst a
        salamander\'s skin is smooth and moist. Many salamanders lay soft eggs in water and their young
        hatch with gills, which metamorphosise like frogs and toads, whilst lizards hatch from a hard
        shell and do not metamorphosise.</string>

    <string name="ex7">Seals and sea lions look similar but have some noticeable
    differences. Sea lions have ear flaps, which seals do not. Sea lions also have
    longer front and back flippers that can rotate, allowing them greater mobility on land. A seal has smaller
        back flippers that do not rotate, so they scoot on their bellies to move on land, almost
        like a caterpillar. Seals are more solitary, quiet and spend much more time in water than sea lions,
        which often gather on land in large groups, barking loudly!</string>

</resources>



